Guide to the Lahiton - Cinema World image archive M2036
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lahiton - Cinema World image archive
1955-1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Lahiton-Cinema World
M2036
38 Linear Feet (89 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box)
Biographical / Historical
Lahiton magazine was conceived in 1969 by two partners, Uri Aloni and David Paz, and was funded by an investment from Avraham Alon, a Ramlah nightclub owner and promoter. The name “Lahiton,” reportedly invented by entertainers Rivka Michaeli and Ehud Manor, combines the Hebrew words for (musical) hit, “lahit” and newspaper, “iton.” In 1976, Lahiton merged with the fan magazine Olam ha-Kolnoa [Cinema World].
Scope and Contents
The collection includes more than 15,000 photographs, most black and white, and more than 5000 color slides. The majority of the images were photographed in Israel between the 1950s and the 1980s, mainly by Israeli photographers. Some of the files contain ephemera such as newspaper clippings and other promotional materials.
Arrangement
Series 1, Cinema, consists of three sub-series: Sub-series 1, Actors; sub-series 2, Films; sub-series 3, Miscellaneous. Series 2, Entertainers. Series 3, Entertainment: Competitions and festivals. Series 4, Foreign visitors to Israel/Foreign celebrities. Series 5, Journalists/Politicians/Military. Series 6, Military entertainment, consists of two sub-series: Sub-series 1, Solo performers; sub-series 2, Bands. Series 7, Miscellaneous categories. Series 8, Music, consists of three sub-series: Sub-series 1, Bands; sub-series 2, Industry photos; sub-series 3, Performers. Series 9, Television, consists of two sub-series: Sub-series 1, Channels & programs; sub-series 2, Actors. Series 10, Theater, consists of two sub-series: Sub-series 1, Actors; sub-series 2, Performances. Series 11, Unsorted images.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Lahiton-Cinema World collection was acquired from Ilan Shaul of Tel-Aviv (represented by the Kedem Auction House, Ltd., of Jerusalem), in 2014.
Lahiton-Cinema World
- Series 1: Cinema
  - Sub-series 1: Actors
    Scope and Contents
    Images of Israeli cinema actors
    - Abbas, Ghassan (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abecassis, Yael (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Abutbul, Alon (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Adar, Aliza (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Agadati, Baruch (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Akselrod, Natan (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Almagor, Gila (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Almagor, Gila (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Almagor, Gila (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alter, Naftali (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Amir, Dani (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Amrani, Gabi (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Ankori, Gilat (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Ansky, Alex (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Arazi, Ami (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Armoni, Dafna (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Arnon, Mordechai (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Astruc, Edity (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Atzmon, Anat (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Atzmon, Anat (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Avivi, Yael (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Avivi, Yael (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Azulay, Hannah (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Barkan, Yehuda (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bar-Shavit, Shlomo (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bar Zohar, Yael (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Bat Adam, Michal (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Bau, Yosef (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Ben Amotz, Naomi (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bikel, Theodore (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Brand, Mike (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Burstyn, Mike (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Burstyn, Mike (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Danuta (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Dantsiger, Maya (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Dattner, Nathan (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Dayan, Asi (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Dayan, Tiki (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Dekel, Dafna (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - DeMarchis, Carlo (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Doron, Eran (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Dotan, Dudu (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Eden, Chana (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Eden, Ilana (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Eden, Rolf (Shimon) (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
    - Eldor, Gabi (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Elian, Yona (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Even-Tov, Amnon (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Fabian, Miri (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Farber, Galit (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Feller, Dana (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Frank, Irit (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Fridman, Dov (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Fridman, Ilana (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Gabai, Sasson (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Gerama, Nisim (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Giat, Moshe (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Giladi, Moti (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Golan, Menachem (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Goldblat, Hanan (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Halprin, Daria (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Harpaz, Anat (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Heiman, Nachum (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Ipale, Aharon (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Ish-Kassit, Moshe (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Ivgy, Moshe (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Katzur, Yftah (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Kaufman, Tali (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Kimhi, Alona (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Kol, Yitshak (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Kraus, Shmulik (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Langford, Caroline (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - Laszlo, Hana (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Lavi, Dalia (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Levanon, Yaud (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Lukov, Didi (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Malka, Dalia (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Marks, Aviva (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Menachem, David (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Michaeli, Rivka (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Mikhaeli, Yvonne (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
    - Mizrahi, Moshe (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Mizrahi, Shaul (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Mor, Tiki (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Moran, Viki (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Moskona, Aryeh (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Nakkara, Salwa (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Nesher, Avi (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Neumann, Rivka (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Nitsani, Yair (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Nagar, Lilit (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Nof, Yigal (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Noy, Zachi (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Obediah, George (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Paz, Shlomo (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Pen, Dalia (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Peres, Uzi (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Perl, Yael (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Perlov, David (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Persof, Nehamyah (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Porat, Ronit (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Rabinovich, Dalia (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Revach, Zeev (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Sally, Uri (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Sassover, Gil (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Segal, Yonatan (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Shaul, Nitza (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Shor, Yael (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Smadar, David (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Sola, Yehudit (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Spivak, Tami (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Suchar, Henia (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Suisa, Meir (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Swan, Gad (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Teomi, Oded (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Topol, Anat (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Topol, Chaim (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Toren, Dan (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Tsahor, Anat (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Tsfati, Noa (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Tsur, Edit (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Turgeman, Dan (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Tzarfati, Asher (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Unikovski, Germaine (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Valinitz, Dalik (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Wagner, Shuli (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Weingarten, Ofra (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Yagil, Gadi (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Zadok, Arnon (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Zeira, Orit (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Zohar, Uri (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Zoharetz, Michal (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Sub-series 2: Films
    Images from Israeli film sets and film stills
    - Aba ganuv אבא גנוב (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Abu al-Banat אבו אל בנאת (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Adam אדם (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Adamah hamah אדמה חמה (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Ad kalot עד כלות (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Ad sof ha-lailah עד סוף הלילה (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Agaf ha-hapalot אגף ההפלות (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Agudat Omane Yisrael (AMI) אגודת אמני ישראל (אמי) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ahavah ilemet אהבה אילמת (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Ahavah le-lo rahamim אהבה ללא רחמים (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Ahavah rishonah nidonah le-kishalon אהבה ראשונה נדונה לכישלון (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Akhalta otah אכלת אותה (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Aleks holeh ahavah אלקס חולה אהבה (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Al hevel dak על חבל דק (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Aliyato shel david lev עלייתו של דוד לב (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Alizah mizrahi עליזה מזרחי (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Al tishali im ani ohev אל תשאלי אם אני אוהב (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Am yisrael hai עם ישראל חי (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Ana lahesh et shemi אנא לחש את שמי (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Ani ohev otakh rozah אני אוהב אותך רוזה (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Ani veha-meahev shel ishti אני והמאהב של אשתי (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Ani yerushalmi אני ירושלמי (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Arianah אריאנה (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Arim ba-shekiah ערים בשקיעה (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Ashanti אשנט (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Asire adam אסירי אדם (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Asire ha-hofesh אסירי החופש (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Atalyah עתליה (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Avanti popolo אווטי פופולו (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Avraham avinu אברהם אבינו (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Azit ha-kalbah ha-tsanhanit עזית הכלבה הצנחנית (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Baal be-ribua בעל בריבוע (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Badranit be-hatsot בדרנית בחצות (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Be-hazarah la-hayim בחזרה לחיים (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Behinat bagrut בחינת בגרות (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Belfer בלפר (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Ben lokeah bat בן לוקח בת (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Billy Two Hats (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Black September (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Bluz la-hofesh ha-gadol בלוז לחופש הגדול (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Boker tov yisrael בוקר טוב ישראל (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bo nefotsets milyon בוא נפוצץ מליון (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Bubah בובה (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - [Cinematographers] (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
    - Derekh ha-nesher דרך הנשר (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Dizengof 99 דיזנגוף 99 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Edut meunas עדות מאונס (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Ehad mi-shelanu אחד משלנו (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - El atsmi אל עצמי (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Elef neshikot ketanot אלף נשיקות קטנות (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Esh dolevet אש דולבת (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Eskimo limon אסקימו לימון (Box 13, Folder 6-9)
    - Esrim ve-ahat shaot be-minkhen עשרים ואחת שעות במינכן (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - La-netsah ester לנצח אסתר (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Every Time We Say Goodbye (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Ezeh yofi shel tsarot איזה יופי של צרות (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Fantasyah al nose romanti פנטסיה על נושא רומנטי (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Fishkeh be-miluim פישקה במילואים (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Flash פלאש (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Flukh פלוך (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Fortunah פורטונה (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Foto roman פוטו רומן (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Givat halfon גבעת חלפון (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - God's Gun (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Ha-arets ha-muvtahat הארץ המובתחת (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Haifa 1983 film festival (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Ha-lahakah הלהקה (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Halomot neurim חלומות נעורים (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Ha-megilah המגילה (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Hamesh-hamesh חמש-חמש (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Ha-metsitsim המציצים (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Ha-horef ha-aharon החורף האחרון (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Ha-penimiyah הפנימיה (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Helem kerav חלם קרב (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Ikvot עקבות (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - I Like Mike (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Ima yehudiyah אמא יהודיה (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Imi ha-generalit אמי הגנרלית (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    - Iris (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Irit-Irit (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Ish rahel איש רחל (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Ish shahor ish lavan איש שחור איש לבן (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Kahol amok כחול עמוק (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Kipur כיפור (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Koko ben 19 קוקו בן 19 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Kompot naalayim קומפוט נעליים (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Koni lemel be-kahir קוני למל בקהיר (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Koni Lemel be-tel-aviv קוני למל בתל אביב (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Lahat ba-mayim להט במים (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Lahats לחץ (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Last American Virgin (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Le-an neelam Daniel Vaks? לאן נעלם דניאל וקס (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Lel ahavah ba-kineret ליל אהבה בכנרת (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Le-lakek 't ha-tut ללקק ת התות (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Lenah לנה (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Lohmot ha-raam לוחמות הרעם (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Lupo be-nyu york לופו בניו יורק (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
    - Magash ha-kesef מגש הכסף (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mahboim מחבואים (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Makat shemesh מכת שמש (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Maks ve-moris מקס ומוריס (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Malkat ha-kevish מלכת הכביש (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Malkat ha-kitah מלכת הכיתה (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Marat shemesh מרת שמש (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Masa alunkot מסע אלונקות (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Matsor מצור (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Me-ahore ha-soragim מאחורי הסורגים (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Mehapeset baal al arba מחפסת בעל על ארבע (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Me-huts la-hok מחוץ לחוק (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Melekh ha-salim מלך הסלים (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Melekh le-yom ehad מלך ליום אחד (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Menaged מנגד (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Ha-meshakhnea המשכנע (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Ha-miyuad המיועד (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Mezimot bi-yerushalayim מזימות בירושלים (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Mikhael sheli מכאל שלי (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Milyoner be-tsarot מליונר בצרות (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Miri מירי (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Mivtsa kahir מבצע קהיר (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Mivtsa shtreyml מבצע שטריימל (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Mivtsa yonatan מבצע יונתן (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Morde ha-or מורדי האור (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Moses the Lawyer (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Mot ha-zar מות הזר (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Naarat ha-parvarim נערת הפרברים (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Nagua נגוע (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Nikmat ha-dam נקמת הדם (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Nes ba-ayarah נס בעיירה (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Nikmato shel itsik finkelshteyn נקמתו של איציק פינקלשטיין (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Nipagesh ba-sivuv ניפגש בסיבוב (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Nisuim fiktivim נישואים פיקטיבים (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Nisuin nusah tel aviv ניסואין נוסח תל אביב (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Orot min ha-derekh אורות מן הדרך (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Or min ha-hefker אור מן ההפקר (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Orvim עורבים (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Ot kayn אות קיין (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Ovdim al ha-olam עובדים על העולם (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Parashat vinshel פרשת וינשל (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Parashat yitshak פרשת יצחק (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Paro veha-eved פרעה והעבד (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Pegishah mikrit פגישה מיקרית (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Perahim פרחים (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Peshitah al entebeh פשיתה על אנטבה (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Pitse bagrut פיצי בגרות (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Sabrah komando סברה קומנדו (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Saharah (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Salah Shabati סלאח שבתי (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Salmoniko סלמוניקו (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Sayarim סיירים (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Seret ve-aruhat boker סרט וארוחת בוקר (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Sheminiyot ba-avir שמיניות באוויר (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Shete etsbaot mi-tsidon שתי אצבעות מצידון (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Shigaon ha-breikdans שגעון הברייקדנס (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Shirat ha-sirenah שירת הסירנה (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Shish koler שיש קולר (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - [Short films] (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Shovarim שוברים (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Sipur intimi סיפור איטימי (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Snuker סנוקר (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Sodah shel yulah סודה של יולה (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sofo shel milton levi סופו של מילטון לוי (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Tealat blaumilkh תעלת בלאומילך (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Temunat matsav תמונת מצב (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Tsalash ha-metoraf צלש המטורף (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Tselilah hozeret צלילה חוזרת (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Tsharli va-hetsi צרלי וחצי (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Tsipore laylah ציפורי לילה (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Zug nasui זוג נשואי (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sub-series 3: Miscellaneous
    Unsorted images and ephemera relating to Israeli cinema
    - Miscellaneous cinema materials (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
- Series 2: Entertainers
  Images of Israeli performers
  - Banai, Yossi (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Dream Team (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Entertainers with their children (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Gaon, Yehoram (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
  - Golan, Menahem (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Goldblatt, Hanan (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Gov, Gidi (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "Ha-teumim" (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Homah u-migdal (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Keshet, Sassi (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
  - Kishon, Ephraim (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Magicians (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Magicians (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Michaeli, Rivka (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Moshinov, Moni (Box 24, Folder 4-5)
  - Nahamias, Hanny (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Nelson, Rafi (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Ophir, Shaike (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
  - Peer, Manny (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Rivlin, Sefi (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Rosenblum, Pnina (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
  - Sassover, Gil (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Shavit, Tzipi (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
  - Topaz, Dudu (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Tzafir, Tuvia (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
- Series 3: Entertainment: Competitions and Festivals
  Images relating to beauty pageants; song festivals; and Eurovision song contests, most sponsored by Lahiton
  - Miss Universe 1976: Rina Mor (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Beauty pageant contestants 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Beauty contests 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Beauty pageant contestants 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Beauty pageant contestants 1981 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Beauty contests 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Hasidic song festivals (Box 28, Folder 8-10)
  - Avival: Spring in Tel Aviv (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Children's song festivals (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Disco championship 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Eurovision 1976 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Eurovision 1977-78 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Eurovision 1979-86 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Festival ha-zemer ha-mizrahi (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
- Series 4: Foreign visitors to Israel/Foreign celebrities
  Images of foreign celebrities, some with their families, on Lahiton-sponsored visits to Israel; public relations images of foreign celebrities in their home countries
  - Adler, Larry (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Adamo (Salvatore) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Ali, Muhammed (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Alpert, Herb (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, Pamela (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Armatrading, Joan (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Aznavour, Charles (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Baez, Joan (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Baez, Joan (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Baker, Josephine (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Baltimora (Italian band) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Bananarama (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Bancroft, Anne (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Bee Gees (Barry Gibb) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Bergman, Ingrid (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Blake, Christopher (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Boomer (canine star) (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Boone, Pat (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Bridges, Jeff (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Bronson, Charles (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Brown, Jim (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Brynner, Yul (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Burr, Raymond (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Burton, LaVar (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Byrne, Gabriel (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Caine, Michael (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Canasta, Chan (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Cardinal, Vin (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Carr, Darlene (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Carradine, David (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Cash, Johnny (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Cassidy, Joanna (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Champagne (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Cher (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Clapton, Eric (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Clayburgh, Jill (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Coburn, James (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Cocker, Joe (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Collins, Lewis (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Conrad, William (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Damon, Cathryn (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Davis, Bette (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Davis Jr., Sammy (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Delon, Alain (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - DeNiro, Robert (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Depardieu, Gerard (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Dewhurst, Colleen (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Dietrich, Marlene (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Divine (Harris Glenn Milstead) (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Dreyfus, Richard (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Dunaway, Faye (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Eastwood, Clint (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Fawcett, Farrah (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Field, Sally (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Fletcher, Louise (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Folkloric Band of Mexico (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Fonda, Jane (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Foreign celebrities with Aharon Ipale (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Foreign celebrities with Tsvikah from Lahiton (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Foreign celebrities with Lahiton Hollywood correspondent Yehudit Solomon (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Fouad, Moharam (Egyptian movie star) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Galway, Don (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Gere, Richard (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Glaser, Paul Michael (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Godunov, Alexander (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Golden Gate (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Gosset, Louis Jr. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Graves, Peter (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Grey, Joel (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Griffith, Melanie (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Groh, David (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Guillaume, Robert (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Hall, Monty (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Hamilton, George (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Harper, Valerie (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Harris, Suzanne (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Havens, Richie (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Hawn, Goldie (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Hayes, Helen (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Hemingway, Margeaux (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Hendrix, Jimi (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Hershey, Barbara (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Heywood, Anne (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Hoskins, Bob (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Hudson, Rock (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Humphries, Les (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Hurt, John (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - King Hussein of Jordan (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Hutton, Timothy (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Imagination (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Impresarios, foreign (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Inglesias, Julio (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Joel, Billy (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Beverly (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Joselito (Jose Jimenez Fernandez) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Kanaly, Steve (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Katz, Omri (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Keegan, Kevin (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - King, Alan (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - King, B.B. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - King, Zalman (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Kingsley, Ben (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Kinski, Klaus (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Kinski, Nastassja (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Kline, Kevin (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Klugman, Jack (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Lange, Ted (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Lennon, John and Yoko Ono (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Lewis, Jerry (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Loren, Sophia (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Macias, Enrico (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Maclean, Don (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Manhattan Transfer (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Marceau, Marcel (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Marillion (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Mastroianni, Marcello (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - McCartney, Paul (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - McLaughlin, John (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 9-11)
  - Moore, Roger (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Mungo Jerry (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Nicole (German singer; Eurovision contest winner) (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - O'Connor, Carrol (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Pakula, Joanna (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Palance, Jack (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Peck, Gregory (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Pesci, Joe (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Pointer, Pricilla (Amy Irving's mother) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Polanski, Roman (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Les Poppys (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Powers, Stephanie (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - PR photos (Box 37, Folder 9-12)
  - Quayle, Anthony (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Ramirez, Ariel (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Rebroff, Ivan (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Remick, Lee (Box 37, Folder 16)